<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrubs Up</string>
    <string name="top_bar">Choose</string>
    <string name="card">Memory Cards</string>
    <string name="show_answer">Click the card to see the answer</string>
    <string name="show_question">Click the answer to see the question again</string>
    <string name="heart">Heart</string>
    <string name="brain">Brain</string>
    <string name="lungs">Lungs</string>
    <string name="previous_button">previous button</string>
    <string name="model_3d">3D Models</string>
    <string name="model_3d_one">3D model</string>
    <string name="Arterial_vessel">Arterial vessel</string>
    <string name="Neuron">Neuron</string>
    <string name="full_body">Full body</string>
    <string name="skeleton">Skeleton</string>
    <string name="eye">Eye</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="word_count">%d/5</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="score">Score: %d</string>
    <string name="question_count">Question %d out of 5</string>
    <string name="ortho">Ortho</string>
    <string name="cardiology">Cardiology</string>
    <string name="neurology">Neurology</string>
    <string name="trauma">Trauma</string>
    <string name="upperlimb">Upper Limb</string>
    <string name="lowerlimb">Lower Limb</string>
    <string name="respiratory">Respiratory System</string>
    <string name="wholeskeleton">Whole Skeleton</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <!-- human body -->
    <string name="Trachea">Trachea</string>
    <string name="Trachea_details">In some terrestrial arthropods, tube that carries air directly to the cells</string>
    <string name="heart_details">Muscular organ that pumps blood to all parts of the body</string>
    <string name="lung_details">One of pair of spongy , saclike organs where gas exchange occurs</string>
    <string name="brrain_details">Control center for the vertebrate body</string>
    <string name="pupil">Pupil</string>
    <string name="pupil_details">Opening in the center of the iris</string>
    <!-- vessel -->
    <string name="rbc">Red Blood Cells (RBC)</string>
    <string name="rbc_details">Red blood cells, or erythrocytes, are the most common type of blood cell. Their primary function is to transport oxygen from the lungs to the bodys tissues and carbon dioxide from the tissues back to the lungs for exhalation.</string>
    <string name="wbc">White Blood Cells (WBC)</string>
    <string name="wbc_details">White blood cells, also known as leukocytes, are a vital part of the immune system. They help the body fight infection and foreign invaders, such as bacteria, viruses, and other pathogens.</string>
    <string name="arteriole_wall">Arteriole Wall</string>
    <string name="arteriole_wall_details">Arterioles are small blood vessels that branch out from arteries and lead to capillaries. The arteriole wall consists of three layers: the tunica intima (inner layer), tunica media (middle layer), and tunica externa (outer layer). These walls are muscular and can contract or dilate to regulate blood flow and blood pressure.</string>
    <!-- neuron -->
    <string name="cell_body">Cell body</string>
    <string name="cell_body_details">The cell nucleus and organelles reside inside the cell body.</string>
    <string name="myelin_sheath">Myelin sheath</string>
    <string name="myelin_sheath_details">Myelinated axons increase the speed of action potentials down the nerve and insulate the fibers to prevent cross talk.</string>
    <string name="dendrite">Dendrite</string>
    <string name="dendrite_details">Several dendrites receive signals from other neurons. If enough signals reach the threshold necessary, an axon potential is initiated and travels down the axon.</string>
    <string name="axon">Myelinate axon</string>
    <string name="axon_details">Οligodendroglial cells are responsible for the synthesis and maintenance of myelin, whereas Schwann cells subserve this role in the peripheral nervous system (PNS).</string>
    <string name="terminal">Axon terminal</string>
    <string name="terminal_details">Axon terminals are the ends of axons which transmit messages to other cells via use of neurotransmitters at synapses</string>
    <!-- heart -->
    <string name="human_heart">Human Heart</string>
    <string name="human_heart_details">The heart is a muscular organ about the size of a fist, located just behind and slightly left of the breastbone. The heart pumps blood through the network of arteries and veins called the cardiovascular system.</string>
    <string name="mitral_valve">Mitral Valve</string>
    <string name="mitral_valve_details">Lets oxygen-rich blood from your lungs pass from the left atrium into the left ventricle.</string>
    <string name="aortic_valve">Aortic valve</string>
    <string name="aortic_valve_details">Opens the way for oxygen-rich blood to pass from the left ventricle into the aorta, your body’s largest artery.</string>
    <string name="choardae_endineae">Chordae Tendineae</string>
    <string name="choardae_endineae_details">Known as the heart strings, are cord-like tendons that connect the papillary muscles to the tricuspid valve and the bicuspid valve in the heart.</string>
    <string name="tricuspid_valve">Tricuspid Valve</string>
    <string name="tricuspid_valve_details">Regulates blood flow between the right atrium and right ventricle.</string>
    <string name="pulmonary">Pulmonary Valve</string>
    <string name="pulmonary_details">Controls blood flow from the right ventricle into the pulmonary arteries, which carry blood to your lungs to pick up oxygen.</string>
    <string name="right_art">Right Atrium</string>
    <string name="right_art_details">The right upper chamber of the heart. The right atrium receives deoxygenated blood from the body through the vena cava and pumps it into the right ventricle which then sends it to the lungs to be oxygenated.</string>
    <string name="right_ven">Right Ventricle</string>
    <string name="right_ven_details">The lower right chamber of the heart that receives deoxygenated blood from the right atrium and pumps it under low pressure into the lungs via the pulmonary artery.</string>
    <string name="left_ven">Left Ventricle</string>
    <string name="left_ven_details">The left lower chamber of the heart that receives blood from the left atrium and pumps it out under high pressure through the aorta to the body.</string>
    <string name="left_art">Left Atrium</string>
    <string name="left_art_details">The upper left chamber of the heart. The left atrium receives oxygenated blood from the lungs and pumps it down into the left ventricle which delivers it to the body.</string>
    <!-- brain -->
    <string name="frontal_lobe">Frontal Lobe</string>
    <string name="frontal_lobe_details">The frontal lobes are important for voluntary movement, expressive language and for managing higher level executive functions. Executive functions refer to a collection of cognitive skills including the capacity to plan, organize, initiate, self-monitor and control one’s responses in order to achieve a goal.</string>
    <string name="parietal_lobe">Parietal Lobe</string>
    <string name="parietal_lobe_details">The parietal lobes can be divided into two functional regions. One involves sensation and perception and the other is concerned with integrating sensory input, primarily with the visual system. The first function integrates sensory information to form a single perception (cognition).</string>
    <string name="temporal">Temporal Lobe</string>
    <string name="temporal_details">Most commonly associated with processing auditory information and with the encoding of memory. The temporal lobes are also believed to play an important role in processing affect/emotions, language, and certain aspects of visual perception.</string>
    <string name="stem">Brain Stem</string>
    <string name="stem_details">The brainstem has many basic functions, including regulation of heart rate, breathing, sleeping, and eating. It also plays a role in conduction. All information relayed from the body to the cerebrum and cerebellum and vice versa must traverse the brainstem.</string>
    <string name="occipital_lobe">Occipital Lobe</string>
    <string name="occipital_lobe_details">The occipital lobe is the part of the human brain responsible for interpreting information from the eyes and turning it into the world as a person sees it.</string>
    <!-- eye -->
    <string name="iris">Iris</string>
    <string name="iris_details">The iris is a flat and ring-shaped membrane, it is Made of densely pigmented posterior double epithelium. This structure Serves as the “diaphragm” of the eye.</string>
    <string name="ciliary">Ciliary body</string>
    <string name="ciliary_details">Ciliary body is a circular structure that extends from the iris (the colored part of the eye). Ciliary Body is divided into two parts : a- The first one is the Ciliary muscle. b- The second one represents Ciliary Processes</string>
    <string name="sclera">Sclera</string>
    <string name="sclera_details">The sclera is the white part of the eye that surrounds the cornea. In fact, the sclera forms more than 80 percent of the surface area of the eyeball, extending from the cornea all the way to the optic nerve, which exits the back of the eye. Only a small portion of the anterior sclera is visible.</string>
    <!-- lungs -->
    <string name="trac">Trachea</string>
    <string name="trac_details">Trachea (TRAY-kee-uh) is a long, U-shaped tube that connects your larynx (voice box) to your lungs. The trachea is often called the windpipe. Its a key part of your respiratory system. When you breathe in, air travels from your nose or mouth through your larynx</string>
    <string name="prbr">Principal bronchus</string>
    <string name="prbr_details">Bronchi have two main (or primary, or first) parts: Right main bronchus is a short, wide air passageway into your right lung. Left main bronchus is a narrow, long passageway into your left lung.</string>
    <string name="cricoid">Cricoid cartilage</string>
    <string name="cricoid_details">The cricoid cartilage is a hyaline cartilage ring which fully encircles the trachea and composes the inferior-most boundary of the laryngeal skeleton. The term “cricoid,” (Greek, krikos meaning “ring-shaped”) refers to the signet-ring resemblance of the cricoid cartilage.</string>
    <!-- skeleton -->
    <string name="ribs">Ribs</string>
    <string name="ribs_details">Your ribcage is assembled from three types of bone - your sternum, 12 pairs of ribs and 12 thoracic vertebrae. All of your ribs attach to your spine, but only the top seven pairs connect to your sternum. These are known as true ribs and they are connected to your sternum by strips of cartilage.</string>
    <string name="cervical_spine">Cervical spine</string>
    <string name="cervical_spine_details">cervical spine is the neck region of your spinal column or backbone. It consists of your first seven bones (C1-C7). Other structures in or around your cervical spine are your intervertebral disks, spinal cord and nerves, muscles, tendons and ligaments.</string>
    <string name="sternum">Sternum</string>
    <string name="sternum_details">The sternum is a partially T-shaped vertical bone that forms the anterior portion of the chest wall centrally. The sternum is divided anatomically into three segments: manubrium, body, and xiphoid process. The sternum connects the ribs via the costal cartilages forming the anterior rib cage</string>


    <!-- QUIZ -->
    <!-- neurology -->
    <string name="brain1">Patient with longstanding history of intermittent headache. What does the image show?</string>
    <string name="brain1_1">Subdural collection</string>
    <string name="brain1_2">Subarachnoid haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain1_3">Normal appearances</string>
    <string name="brain1_4">Interventricular haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain2">History of head injury. Patient unconscious. Which statement is true?</string>
    <string name="brain2_1">There is no evidence of mass effect</string>
    <string name="brain2_2">The scan shows subarachnoid haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain2_3">Changing window settings would help clarify the diagnosis</string>
    <string name="brain2_4">A history of anticoagulation is irrelevant in this setting</string>
    <string name="brain3">Patient with a sudden onset of hemianopia. What does this pre-contrast CT brain image demonstrate?</string>
    <string name="brain3_1">Basal ganglia infarct</string>
    <string name="brain3_2">Left occipital intracerebral haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain3_3">Abnormal calcification</string>
    <string name="brain3_4">An enhancing mass</string>
    <string name="brain4">Which description most accurately describes the findings on these two images?</string>
    <string name="brain4_1">Increased density consistent with a subdural collection</string>
    <string name="brain4_2">Multiple areas of enhancement due to metastases</string>
    <string name="brain4_3">Areas of abnormally low density surrounded by enhancement post IV-contrast</string>
    <string name="brain4_4">Increased density consistent with an acute primary intracerebral haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain5">Patient with history of recent head injury. What does this scan show?</string>
    <string name="brain5_1">Intracerebral haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain5_2">Scalp haematoma</string>
    <string name="brain5_3">Parafalcine extra-axial haemorrhage</string>
    <string name="brain5_4">Subarachnoid haemorrhage</string>


    <!-- lungs -->
    <string name="lungs1">Which finding is present on this image?</string>
    <string name="lungs1_1">Normal X-ray image</string>
    <string name="lungs1_2">Sail sign</string>
    <string name="lungs1_3">Pneumothorax</string>
    <string name="lungs1_4">Meniscus sign</string>
    <string name="lungs2">Which finding is present on this detail image of the left lung?</string>
    <string name="lungs2_1">Mesothelioma</string>
    <string name="lungs2_2">Asbestosis</string>
    <string name="lungs2_3">Pleural effusion</string>
    <string name="lungs2_4">Calcified pleural plaques</string>
    <string name="lungs3">20 year old female with high temperature and cough. Which answer best describes the appearance?</string>
    <string name="lungs3_1">Normal</string>
    <string name="lungs3_2">Image inadequate due to patient rotation</string>
    <string name="lungs3_3">Pleural effusion</string>
    <string name="lungs3_4">Consolidation</string>
    <string name="lungs4">Which finding is present?</string>
    <string name="lungs4_1">Normal chest X-ray</string>
    <string name="lungs4_2">Pectus excavatum</string>
    <string name="lungs4_3">Azygos fissure</string>
    <string name="lungs4_4">Free gas under the diaphragm</string>
    <string name="lungs5">Cough, weight loss and finger clubbing. Which statement is true?</string>
    <string name="lungs5_1">The image is diagnostic of lung cancer</string>
    <string name="lungs5_2">The image is diagnostic of pneumonia</string>
    <string name="lungs5_3">Blunting of the costophrenic angles is due to pleural effusions</string>
    <string name="lungs5_4">The lungs are hyperexpanded</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="you_scored">\"You scored: %d\"</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>

    <!-- Whole Skeleton -->
    <string name="skeleton1">Fall onto face. Painful left cheek area. OM and OM-30 views.</string>
    <string name="skeleton1_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton1_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton2">Inversion injury to ankle. Unable to bear weight. AP and lateral views.</string>
    <string name="skeleton2_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton2_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton3">Fall on outstretched hand. Pain and restricted shoulder abduction. 2 AP clavicle views.</string>
    <string name="skeleton3_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton3_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton4">Fall with direct trauma to knee. Pain, swelling and reduced knee movement. AP and horizontal beam lateral views.</string>
    <string name="skeleton4_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton4_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton5">Flexion/extension injury to neck. Single open-mouth odontoid peg views (other views were normal).</string>
    <string name="skeleton5_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="skeleton5_2">No injury</string>

    <!-- Upper Limb -->
    <string name="upper1">Punch injury to hand. DP and Oblique views.</string>
    <string name="upper1_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="upper1_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="upper2">Fall on shoulder. Pain and reduced range of movement. AP and Axial views.</string>
    <string name="upper2_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="upper2_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="upper3">Fall on outstretched hand. Clavicle pain and tenderness. 2 AP views.</string>
    <string name="upper3_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="upper3_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="upper4">Fall on outstretched hand. Painful and tender forearm. AP and Lateral views.</string>
    <string name="upper4_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="upper4_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="upper5">Injury to elbow when intoxicated. Wound to skin. AP and Lateral views.</string>
    <string name="upper5_1">Foreign body</string>
    <string name="upper5_2">No foreign body</string>

    <!-- Lower Limb -->
    <string name="lower1">Twisted ankle. Pain medially and laterally. AP and lateral views.</string>
    <string name="lower1_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="lower1_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="lower2">Twisting injury. Painful foot. DP and oblique views.</string>
    <string name="lower2_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="lower2_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="lower3">Patient confused. Fall. Pain in hip. AP view of the pelvis.</string>
    <string name="lower3_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="lower3_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="lower4">Hyperextension injury to knee. Pain and tenderness medially. AP and lateral views.</string>
    <string name="lower4_1">Injury</string>
    <string name="lower4_2">No injury</string>
    <string name="lower5">Twisting injury to ankle. Pain and tenderness. Unable to walk. Single AP view (other views were normal).</string>
    <string name="lower5_1">Foreign body</string>
    <string name="lower5_2">No foreign body</string>

    <!-- CARDS -->
    <!-- arterial vessel -->
    <string name="artv_q1">What are Venae Cavae?</string>
    <string name="artv_a1">Largest veins in the body, formed from the consecutive merging of smaller veins. Includes the superior (upper) and inferior (lower) vena cava.</string>
    <string name="artv_q2">Common Iliac Arteries</string>
    <string name="artv_a2">Two arteries (left and right) branching off of the end of the abdominal aorta near the ilium. Supplies oxygenated blood to the rectum, bladder, reproductive organs, legs, and feet.</string>
    <string name="artv_q3">Descending Aorta</string>
    <string name="artv_a3">The portion of the aorta occurring after the aortic arch that is made up of the thoracic (in the thorax of the body) and abdominal (in the abdominal cavity of the body) aorta.</string>
    <string name="artv_q4">Aortic Arch</string>
    <string name="artv_a4">A branching portion of the aorta that is shaped like an upside-down U. Responsible for supplying the arms, neck, head, and brain with oxygenated blood.</string>
    <string name="artv_q5">Coronary Arteries</string>
    <string name="artv_a5">Two arteries (left and right) that carry oxygenated blood to the heart muscle. When blocked due to plaque build-up, can lead to a heart attack.</string>
    <string name="artv_q6">Aorta</string>
    <string name="artv_a6">The largest artery found in the body which functions in carrying blood away from the heart from the left ventricle to the rest of the body.</string>
    <string name="artv_q7">Pulmonary Trunk</string>
    <string name="artv_a7">A large artery that fills with deoxygenated blood from the right ventricle of the heart following the opening of the pulmonary semilunar valve.Connects to the left and right pulmonary arteries.</string>

    <!-- neuron -->
    <string name="neur_q1">What are Dendrites?</string>
    <string name="neur_a1">Dendrites are extensions leading toward cell body that receives signal from other neurons and send them to the cell body.</string>
    <string name="neur_q2">Cell body</string>
    <string name="neur_a2">Part of neuron that holds the nucleus as well as other organelles, also called the soma.</string>
    <string name="neur_q3">Nucleus</string>
    <string name="neur_a3">Contains the genetic material of the neuron.</string>
    <string name="neur_q4">Axon</string>
    <string name="neur_a4">A long strand attached to the cell body. Conducts nerve impulses away from the cell body toward other neurons or effectors.</string>
    <string name="neur_q5">Myelin sheath</string>
    <string name="neur_a5">A lipid layer around the axon. It carries the message to one of these lipids to another, making transporting an impulse efficient.</string>
    <string name="neur_q6">Action Potential</string>
    <string name="neur_a6">Neurons transmit messages in the form of electrochemical impulses called an action potential.</string>
    <string name="neur_q7">Central Nervous System</string>
    <string name="neur_a7">This consists of the brain and spinal cord. This is the ultimate control center for all human behavior.</string>

    <!-- heart -->
    <string name="heart_q1">Pulmonary Artery</string>
    <string name="heart_a1">Carries deoxygentated blood from the heart to the lungs.</string>
    <string name="heart_q2">Left Atrium</string>
    <string name="heart_a2">Receives oxygen-rich blood from the lungs through the four pulmonary veins.</string>
    <string name="heart_q3">The two valves that blood coming from the body passes.</string>
    <string name="heart_a3">Tricuspid valve and the pulmonary semilunar valve.</string>
    <string name="heart_q4">The two valves that blood coming from the lungs passes.</string>
    <string name="heart_a4">Mitral (bicuspid) valve and the aortic semilunar valve.</string>
    <string name="heart_q5">The primary pumping chambers of the heart.</string>
    <string name="heart_a5">Ventricles</string>
    <string name="heart_q6">Blood is forced into this area when the ventricle is filled.</string>
    <string name="heart_a6">Artery</string>
    <string name="heart_q7">Named for the three flaps that separate the right atrium and right ventricle.</string>
    <string name="heart_a7">Tricuspid valve</string>

    <!-- brain -->
    <string name="brain_q1">Identify the system of the brain that controls emotion and motivation.</string>
    <string name="brain_a1">The Limbic System.</string>
    <string name="brain_q2">Name the 4 parts of the brain involved in basic functions.</string>
    <string name="brain_a2">Brainstem, Thalamus, Reticular Formation and Cerebellum.</string>
    <string name="brain_q3">Identify the primary function of the Occipital Lobe.</string>
    <string name="brain_a3">Processes information received from sight.</string>
    <string name="brain_q4">Identify the primary functions of the Parietal Lobe.</string>
    <string name="brain_a4">Processes information received from touch.</string>
    <string name="brain_q5">Identify the primary function of the Temporal Lobe.</string>
    <string name="brain_a5">Processes the information we hear.</string>
    <string name="brain_q6">What is the difference between a gyrus and a sulcus?</string>
    <string name="brain_a6">A gyrus is a bump in the brain, a sulcus is a groove.</string>
    <string name="brain_q7">Identify the primary function of the Thalamus.</string>
    <string name="brain_a7">Forwards information from the senses to other parts of the brain.</string>

    <!-- eye -->
    <string name="eye_q1">Cornea</string>
    <string name="eye_a1">The outermost lens of the eye that focuses light into the inner eye and protects it from harmful matter.</string>
    <string name="eye_q2">Retina</string>
    <string name="eye_a2">The light sensitive layer within the eye that converts images into electrical signals.</string>
    <string name="eye_q3">Pupil</string>
    <string name="eye_a3">The hole located in the iris that changes size to allow different amounts of light into the inner eye.</string>
    <string name="eye_q4">Iris</string>
    <string name="eye_a4">The colorful structure of the eye that changes the shape of the pupil to allow for different amounts of light to enter the inner eye.</string>
    <string name="eye_q5">Ciliary Body (muscle)</string>
    <string name="eye_a5">A muscle that controls the shape of the lens to better focus the light onto the retina of the inner eye.</string>
    <string name="eye_q6">Lens</string>
    <string name="eye_a6">The transparent orb within the eye that refracts light to the retina of the eye.</string>
    <string name="eye_q7">Optic Nerve</string>
    <string name="eye_a7">The nerve at the back of the eye that transports electric signals to the brain.</string>

    <!-- lungs -->
    <string name="lungs_q1">Epiglottis</string>
    <string name="lungs_a1">Prevents entry of liquids or solid food through glottis so that food/ liquid would not enter lungs.</string>
    <string name="lungs_q2">Trachea (windpipe)</string>
    <string name="lungs_a2">Tough flexible tube, protects airway, also prevent collapse or expansion of airway as pressure change in respiratory system. Transports air down the vertebra towards the lungs.</string>
    <string name="lungs_q3">What is an obstructive disease?</string>
    <string name="lungs_a3">Persistent slowing of airflow during breathing.</string>
    <string name="lungs_q4">What is spirometry?</string>
    <string name="lungs_a4">An objective measurement of lung function.</string>
    <string name="lungs_q5">Bronchi</string>
    <string name="lungs_a5">Airway passages that conduct air into the lungs (have cartilage).</string>
    <string name="lungs_q6">Bronchioles</string>
    <string name="lungs_a6">Branches of the bronchi, the first passageways by which the air passes through the nose or mouth into the air sacs of the lungs (no cartilage).</string>
    <string name="lungs_q7">Pharynx</string>
    <string name="lungs_a7">The throat. A chamber shared by the digestive and respiratory systems, where materials entering the digestive tract pass through.</string>

    <!-- skeleton -->
    <string name="sk_q1">What is the axilla?</string>
    <string name="sk_a1">The pyramidal space below the shoulder joint - provides passage for the vessels and nerves going to and from the upper limb.</string>
    <string name="sk_q2">At which anatomical point does the axillary artery begin?</string>
    <string name="sk_a2">The lateral border of the 1st rib.</string>
    <string name="sk_q3">The axillary artery continues beyond the axilla as which vessel?</string>
    <string name="sk_a3">Brachial artery</string>
    <string name="sk_q4">Name the roots of the brachial plexus?</string>
    <string name="sk_a4">Anterior rami of C5-T1.</string>
    <string name="sk_q5">What is Erb’s point?</string>
    <string name="sk_a5">The site of the upper trunk of the brachial plexus (2–3cm above the clavicle).</string>
    <string name="sk_q6">Name the muscles in the superficial group of the anterior forearm.</string>
    <string name="sk_a6">Pronator teres, Flexor carpi radialis, Palmaris longus and Flexor carpi ulnaris.</string>
    <string name="sk_q7">What are the superficial muscles of the anterior forearm attached to?</string>
    <string name="sk_a7">The medial epicondyle of the humerus by the common flexor tenson.</string>

    <!-- full body -->
    <string name="fl_q1">Lungs</string>
    <string name="fl_a1">Lungs are the pair of spongy, pinkish-gray organs in our chest. When we inhale (breathe in), air enters our lungs and oxygen from that air moves to our blood.</string>
    <string name="fl_q2">Heart</string>
    <string name="fl_a2">The heart is a vital organ. It is a muscle that pumps blood to all parts of human body. The blood pumped by the heart provides the human body with the oxygen and nutrients it needs to function.</string>
    <string name="fl_q3">Trachea</string>
    <string name="fl_a3">It is a key part of our respiratory system. When we breathe in, air travels from our nose or mouth through our larynx. It then passes through our trachea to our bronchi.</string>
    <string name="fl_q4">Brain</string>
    <string name="fl_a4">The brain is a complex organ that controls thought, memory, emotion, touch, motor skills, vision, breathing, temperature, hunger and every process that regulates our body.</string>
    <string name="fl_q5">Pupil</string>
    <string name="fl_a5">The round opening in the center of the iris.</string>
    <string name="fl_q6">Stomach</string>
    <string name="fl_a6">The stomach is an important organ and the most dilated portion of the digestive system. The esophagus precedes it, and the small intestine follows.</string>
    <string name="fl_q7">Pancreas</string>
    <string name="fl_a7">The pancreas has dual roles, it is an organ of the digestive system and of the endocrine system.</string>
</resources>